<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>HUHU CODESIGN X LAB</title>
  
  <subtitle>Stay Inspired</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:22.699Z</updated>
  <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Siying Hu</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>BeUpStanding</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/12/BeUpStanding/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/12/BeUpStanding/</id>
    <published>2019-04-11T22:46:15.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:22.699Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2018 - November 2018]<br>Course: Design Computing Studio 3 - Build</p><p>“BeAppStanding” is an iOS mobile application to further help the target users to sit less and stand more. This application and physical prototype were development by using native platforms (Swift,Xcode). The key component of my responsibility is to consider how to enhance the user experience and design the data visualisation by using emotion design and interface usability. In terms of it, the system can improve the cognition of target audience.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>BeAppStanding is the project initiated by Professor Genevieve Healy from the Public Health School at the University of Queensland. Professor Healy and her colleagues have created the BeUpStanding project in order to raise people’s awareness of sit less and stand more. This project, BeAppStanding, was created as the extension of the Be Up Standing project, the goal of this project is to create an iOS mobile application to further help the target users to sit less and stand more. </p><p>The solution for the project was to develop an iOS mobile application, the critical features of this application are “Personal Activity Goal” and “Team Activity Goal”. The application allows users to create the standing activity goal by setting how many times they want to stand up and the interval during a day, then the application will remind users to stand up and complete a set of activity by sending them a notification. In addition, users of the application are allowed to invite their friends or colleagues to form into an activity group and the team leader can create a team activity goal for each team member to complete, this feature was designed to encourage users to complete more activity goal. </p><p>The main target users of this application are office workers who spend plenty of time on sitting at office. Another target group for the application is the university students who also spend a huge amount of time on sitting for study. Nevertheless, this application is also targeting the people who constantly spend their time on sitting and have not enough exercise as this application aims to encourage people to stand more and be healthier. Since the main target users are the office workers, the main context of using the BeAppStanding application is during office hours when office workers spend most of time on sitting by the desk. The idea was to let the users to set up the activity goal after arriving in the office and starting to work, the application will start working and send push notification to users’ mobile phone as a reminder for standing. </p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Wiki</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href>Product Introduction Website</a><br><a href="https://youtu.be/UndHM9XU8ck" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Introduction Video</a><br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/vuhtxIZ.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Exhibition Brochure 1</a><br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/PGL4qVu.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Exhibition Brochure 2</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="Teammates"><a href="#Teammates" class="headerlink" title="Teammates"></a>Teammates</h2><p>Linlin Deng, Jing Dong, Yaohui Dong, Siying Hu, Quan Liu, Tianyu Liu, Jiacheng Peng, Yuhua Peng, Yudie Zhang</p><h2 id="My-Contribution"><a href="#My-Contribution" class="headerlink" title="My Contribution"></a>My Contribution</h2><ul><li>Background Research: healthcare domain and target user research.</li><li>Design user interfaces and prototype to improve user productivity, discoverability and simplicity.Icon design and official logo design.</li><li>Create alternative design solutions, evaluating them to choose the best approach.</li><li>Develop UX/UI documentation (i.e. use cases, wire frames, conceptual models, user interaction flow diagrams, page schematics, prototypes).</li><li>Analyze quantitative data from user research to intelligently iterate on products.</li><li>Mobile App development using native platforms (Swift,Xcode) with teammates;</li><li>Work with project teams throughout Agile;</li><li>Used Git for version control across common source code used by developers.  </li></ul><h2 id="Project-Description"><a href="#Project-Description" class="headerlink" title="Project Description"></a>Project Description</h2><h4 id="Application-Overview"><a href="#Application-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Application Overview"></a>Application Overview</h4><p>I designed and implemented the Medium-fidelity to High-fidelity prototype of the application independently using Adobe suit and conducted conceptual model based on user testing. Additionally, I learnt how to use the Swift to build an IOS application by using the Xcode.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/zgRXzRr.png" alt><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/wiH2GvW.png" alt></p><p>By the end of this project, our team completed and provided a working application which can meet current requirements from product owner. The main features of the application have all been successfully deployed to the final product, main features including:</p><ol><li>Sign up and login</li><li>Personal Activity Goal</li><li>Team Activity Goal</li><li>Activity Goal Data Visualisation for both personal and team– Pending Tree</li><li>Account Management</li><li>Award System</li></ol><p>However, despite the full effort from our team and the application is meeting the major requirements of product owner, there are still some defects existed for the application due to the lack of development time. Firstly, the development team initially wanted the function which allows the user to login to the application with their third-party account, such as Google account and Facebook account, this function failed to implemented into the final product. Secondly, the function of setting activity goal failed to match the original design idea, initially the team wanted this function to allow user not just quickly set up an activity goal, but also customize their activity goal by editing more features such as start time and finish time of the activity goal, current function only allows a basic setting for the activity goal. Thirdly, although the team function is working and reaching its original design intention, users will not receive the notification of a team invitation, so currently they have no ability to reject the team invitation; users will not be invited to a team if they already enrolled in another team, but if they were invited to a team that they not intended to join, they have to manually sign out the team by accessing the management page.</p><h4 id="Research-Design-Assessment"><a href="#Research-Design-Assessment" class="headerlink" title="Research/Design Assessment"></a>Research/Design Assessment</h4><p>In this project, the target is to design an iOS mobile application which is able to assist and encourage users with monitoring their daily stand up tasks by setting activity goal individually. Notification function which is one of the key designs of the BeAppStanding application to remind users of doing tasks in time. In addition, users are allowed perform team activity by forming a group. Team activity goal can be set by the team leader who creates the team. This unique design can greatly enhances user experience by allowing users to do activities with friends or colleagues. In the design process, we focus on convenience and interaction. All the main functions are deigned to put in ToDo page altogether which is easy to maintain and viewed by users. Design of Done page enables users to view their daily activity within 12 month calendar. Initially, only white, blue and red colours are used in the user interface because we considered that office workers prefer clearer and simpler visual feelings than complex design. However as the colour purple has been considered strongly related to the image of UQ, thus the UI design was re-designed so that users can see purple elements in some areas which aims to fit with UQ style. shows the changes of UI design.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/tDx3f9Z.png" alt="picture"></p><p>I got the feedback of adding gamification elements to the data visualization in our application after first critique. We recognized that the advice is very valuable for the application so that after confirming with our client, we decided to use animated falling leaves from tree to replace the visualised data in the application. This tree was named ‘Pending Tree’. Animated falling leaves from tree enable users to interact with data more directly with better understanding of operational standing activities and users’ own completion status. It changes the previous design of visualised data that which was not interactive enough. Previous design is shown in below.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/20qvXHB.png" alt="picture"></p><p>The tree will initially have 9 leaves, and keep current state if user keep finishing all the tasks every day. If user did not complete all the tasks in a day, tree will lose leaves. The leaves will grow back when user finish all the set plan in three days. The core design of this part improved the conventional sport Apps which are in lack of amusement elements, difficult to maintain and these functions motivate users to do activities continuously. In the design process, we selected big palm tree with green leaves as the symbol image. Palm tree grows in warm and coastal places which suits the image of Queensland’s warm and sunny weather. Green always represent refreshment which is the core concept of this application. Animated design was used to model the real tree, if user did not give them enough nutrition and water the leaves will fall. I applied this concept to our application that if user did not complete the tasks, leaves will fall however if user finish the tasks (give them enough nutrition and water) the leaves will growing back.<br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Lhqgg83.png" alt="picture"><br>Icon of our application is also one of the important design parts. I redesign twice during the development process. Concepts like high-recognizable, high-resolution, visual consistent are applied in our deign. In the previous design we choose to use green or orange for the icon however I consider that purple is more fitted with UQ style, thus ultimate UQ’s symbol colour purple was selected to fill the most parts of the icon. </p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/hicTLbX.png" alt="picture"></p><h4 id="Updated-system-architecture-diagram"><a href="#Updated-system-architecture-diagram" class="headerlink" title="Updated system architecture diagram"></a>Updated system architecture diagram</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Rpa3mjW.png" alt></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2018 - November 2018]&lt;br&gt;Course: Design Computing Studio 3 - Build&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“BeAppStanding” is an iOS mobile application to further help the target users to sit less and stand more. This application and physical prototype were development by using native platforms (Swift,Xcode). The key component of my responsibility is to consider how to enhance the user experience and design the data visualisation by using emotion design and interface usability. In terms of it, the system can improve the cognition of target audience.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Completed Projects" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Completed-Projects/"/>
    
    
      <category term="App" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/App/"/>
    
      <category term="Healthcare" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Healthcare/"/>
    
      <category term="Xcode" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Xcode/"/>
    
      <category term="Swift" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Swift/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Familiar Stranger</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/12/Familiar-Stranger/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/12/Familiar-Stranger/</id>
    <published>2019-04-11T22:45:44.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:37.338Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2018 - November 2018]<br>Course Name: Social &amp; Mobile Computing</p><p>“Familiar Stranger” is a design concept which try to evoke people’s self-awareness of mobile addiction. It includes a IOS mobile app prototype and  a smart case which made by RFduino.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>Because of the development of mobile technology, People’s lives are closely connected to mobile phones. At the same time, the trend of young people and teenagers gradually become the main force of mobile addiction. These people are passionate about communicating with friends and sharing their lives on the social media of mobile Phones. It is precisely for this reason that they are compressed in real life with people’s Real communication time, and have less chance to communicate with their peers. After an investigation, most students seldom or never try to take the initiative to get in-depth communication with classmates in the same classroom. Even if they all recognise each other, they are also the most familiar Strangers. Our team studied domain focus on social media addiction, and delve into and analyse the causes and effects of this Phenomenon. At the same time, our team was committed to developing a system or equipment to assist in increasing people’s face-to-face communication opportunities. </p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Wiki</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/7Si50Dv.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Conference Poster</a><br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/JAZULol.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brochure 1</a><br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/t4P6sEz.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brochure 2</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="Teammates"><a href="#Teammates" class="headerlink" title="Teammates"></a>Teammates</h2><p>Shiqi Zheng,Yue Feng,Siying Hu,Muhammad Afiq Ainuddin Mohd Khashim</p><h2 id="My-Contribution"><a href="#My-Contribution" class="headerlink" title="My Contribution"></a>My Contribution</h2><ul><li>Run Qualitative and quantitative user research to better understand the problem and get inspired</li><li>Translate concepts into interactive prototypes and iterate;</li><li>Data analysis for different IoT protocols test；</li><li>Physical prototyping developing;</li><li>UX/UI, Wireframing, Application Flows;</li><li>Learn using Arduino Uno and different sensors to detect the data, and then send to a computer or phone using different IOT protocols.</li><li>RFduino and Processing development and electronics on interactive installations requiring physical interactions;</li></ul><h2 id="Project-Description"><a href="#Project-Description" class="headerlink" title="Project Description"></a>Project Description</h2><h4 id="Prototype-Overview"><a href="#Prototype-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Prototype Overview"></a>Prototype Overview</h4><p>As we talked with Tutor and researched before, social textile as an inspiration for us to develop a design opportunity named “familiar stranger”. Our purpose is bringing people to build a new relationship and maintain their friendship in the real world instead of over-relying on social media application. Many people that they meet same people every day in the same place like in the school, the bus station but they never talked with each other or they lack the opportunity to chat with others. Our concept provides a chance for them to communicate with those people and enable them not addicted to social media.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/pRUGyRr.png" alt></p><p>In order to make our concept more attractive to inhabitants, our team member did a questionnaire to ascertain the form of our design, which is phone case. Hence, we linked our idea with the phone case that showed the above pictures. Candidates who have the same phone case they could adjust their current status with emoji such as happy to talk, sad today, really do not want to talk to anyone and etc, which they change the status and people could see their current status to choose whether or not chat with someone.</p><h4 id="Scenario"><a href="#Scenario" class="headerlink" title="Scenario"></a>Scenario</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/rehqoZc.png" alt></p><h4 id="Physical-Prototype"><a href="#Physical-Prototype" class="headerlink" title="Physical Prototype"></a>Physical Prototype</h4><p>The initial hypothesis of our group is to create a prototype of the mobile phone case that simulates the following figure, which consists of two parts, one is to display the light function of different colours, and the other is the display which can display different expression packs. The phone case which can display the users’ emotion, green means they are willing to chat with others, red means do not want to be disturbed. The user can change their emotion by click on the small button on the side of the phone case. People who see other’s phone case display the green light can talk with them without hesitation, while for those who make their phone case display red light can avoid some embarrassing situations.Thus, I build the physical prototype by using the RFduino and sensoring design.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/DTLzhMO.jpg?1" alt></p><p>The entire device was divided into two parts, one is an internal structure that contains the transformed lights controlled by RFdunio. One was an external structure, mainly to simulate the production of a mobile phone case.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/XoQfHzI.jpg?1" alt></p><p>This is the screen that I have intended to display the emojis that user choose. Due to the time limitation, I did not achieve our goal, but I will research and try to implement this function in the future.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/YbgPhfm.jpg?1" alt></p><h4 id="Code-Guide"><a href="#Code-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Code Guide"></a>Code Guide</h4><p>In order to achieve our concept, I set up two device in two file of Arduino named social_host and social_device. Then we initialised the Rfdunio in two file. More details ca view in the github. Like below:</p><figure class="highlight plain"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">device_t role = DEVICE0;</span><br><span class="line">device_t role = HOST;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>Then we set up the three light in social_device.</p><figure class="highlight plain"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br><span class="line">5</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">int red_led = 2;</span><br><span class="line">int green_led = 3;</span><br><span class="line">int blue_led = 4;</span><br><span class="line">int current_led = red_led;</span><br><span class="line">char ledToSend = 0;</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>Next, we set up three pinmode for pressing in two file. Like:</p><figure class="highlight plain"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br><span class="line">4</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">void setup() &#123; pinMode(button_a, INPUT);</span><br><span class="line">pinMode(red_led, OUTPUT);</span><br><span class="line">pinMode(green_led, OUTPUT);</span><br><span class="line">pinMode(blue_led, OUTPUT);</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2018 - November 2018]&lt;br&gt;Course Name: Social &amp;amp; Mobile Computing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Familiar Stranger” is a design concept which try to evoke people’s self-awareness of mobile addiction. It includes a IOS mobile app prototype and  a smart case which made by RFduino.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Completed Projects" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Completed-Projects/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Social &amp; Mobile Computing" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Social-Mobile-Computing/"/>
    
      <category term="Research" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Research/"/>
    
      <category term="RFduino" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/RFduino/"/>
    
      <category term="Prototype" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Prototype/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Super Survivor 2.5D Game</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/09/Super-Survivor-2-5D-Game/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/09/Super-Survivor-2-5D-Game/</id>
    <published>2019-04-09T12:41:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:53.839Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2018 - November 2018]<br>Course: Digital Prototyping </p><p>“Super Survivor Game” is a small map adventure game of website. It was built by using the The HTML5 Creation Engine(PixiJS) and involve physical interaction by using the MakeyMakey.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>“Super Survivor Game” is a small map adventure game of website. It was built by using the The HTML5 Creation Engine(PixiJS) and involve some form of physical interaction by using the MakeyMakey. Using the statement provided to my game by the Game Generator at <a href="http://orteil.dashnet.org/gamegen" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://orteil.dashnet.org/gamegen</a>.</p><p>The protagonist of the game is a different kind of small box, the player needs to manipulate the red small box to move and avoid multiple small black boxes of attack. At the same time, players need to control the small red box to find a symbol of the “survival package” of the yellow box, and carry a small yellow box to move. Within the specified time, when the player places the yellow box in the correct position of the map and collides with the small black box, the movement of the small black box group can be stopped immediately. Finally, the player wins the game. </p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Wiki</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href="https://youtu.be/Yqi4to2kWCs" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Prototype 1: Video Prototype</a><br><a href>Prototype 2: Interactive Prototype 1</a><br><a href>Prototype 3: Interactive Prototype 2</a><br><a href>Prototype 4: Interactive Prototype 3</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="Prototype-1"><a href="#Prototype-1" class="headerlink" title="Prototype 1"></a>Prototype 1</h2><p>I built a video prototype to test implementation of an idea. And also produce a video that communicates my ideas for the game.<br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/DfWsF9C.png" alt></p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/W27uayY.png" alt></p><p><a href="https://youtu.be/Yqi4to2kWCs" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Prototype 1: Video Prototype</a></p><h2 id="Prototype-2"><a href="#Prototype-2" class="headerlink" title="Prototype 2"></a>Prototype 2</h2><p>I created an interactive prototype of my application interface that considers the key user functions, tasks and/or interactions. I was aiming to implement a complete or polished interface. However, functionality should be completed to a level that allows for clear understanding<br>of the elements being evaluated. Thus, when I was deciding on the aspect to be prototyped, consider what it is I want to know about how people would engage/interact with the game interface. According to this, I also created multiple prototypes to evaluate variations in functionality, task flow and interaction methods. As this is an early prototype, the design of the interface used placeholder and wireframe graphics to represent interface elements.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/rNYW0Ff.png" alt><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/WiDcXSR.png" alt></p><h2 id="Prototype-3"><a href="#Prototype-3" class="headerlink" title="Prototype 3"></a>Prototype 3</h2><p>I developed a prototype to evaluate the intended physical (non-digital) inputs/outputs of my game application. The key issues what I thinking about is the physical interactions should be appropriate to the game concept. And it should be prototyped to a standard that allows for useful evaluation. Another problem I need to address - which is the intended physical interaction of my game. In this process, I want to test the physical interaction/input method separate to the interface, and I also want to test how that physical input is represented back to the user through the interface. </p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Q7urssY.png" alt><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/ebS91q4.jpg?1" alt></p><h2 id="Prototype-4"><a href="#Prototype-4" class="headerlink" title="Prototype 4"></a>Prototype 4</h2><p>In the last step, I did the Dark-horse prototype. Because I felt that my concept is suffering from a lack of inspiration. Maybe it can provided some good idea for me to refine my game according to the feedback.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/mdoAk4W.jpg" alt></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2018 - November 2018]&lt;br&gt;Course: Digital Prototyping &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Super Survivor Game” is a small map adventure game of website. It was built by using the The HTML5 Creation Engine(PixiJS) and involve physical interaction by using the MakeyMakey.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Fun Project" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Fun-Project/"/>
    
    
      <category term="HCI" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/HCI/"/>
    
      <category term="website" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/website/"/>
    
      <category term="PixiJS" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/PixiJS/"/>
    
      <category term="2.5D" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/2-5D/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Anxiety Eliminator Game</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/09/Anxiety-Eliminator-Game/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/09/Anxiety-Eliminator-Game/</id>
    <published>2019-04-09T12:41:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:02.369Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2017 - November 2017]</p><p> “Anxiety Eliminator” is an interactive&amp;digital game prototype built by using the Unity(C#) and involve some forms of physical interaction by using the Leap Motion and MakeyMakey.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>Anxiety Eliminator is an interactive &amp; digital game prototype built by using the Unity and involve some form of physical interaction by using the Leap Motion and MakeyMakey. Players need to match the music and tap the schematic pattern in the game prototype. The player operates the digital game prototype mainly by their gestures activities or by hitting physical objects.</p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Wiki</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href>Download</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="The-Game-Form"><a href="#The-Game-Form" class="headerlink" title="The Game Form"></a>The Game Form</h2><p>The form of this game consist on two part - Unity product and Physical Input, which connect together by MakeyMakey. In this test, the change of form is the physical input. I use the Twister’s game blanket as a wider control area and use an insulating tape to hold the touch points of aluminum foil onto the blanket. Finally, use the wire to connect the touch point to MakeyMakey.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/eBhjdbc.png" alt><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/5Id3T8E.png" alt><br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/7f5s9Z0.png" alt></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2017 - November 2017]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “Anxiety Eliminator” is an interactive&amp;amp;digital game prototype built by using the Unity(C#) and involve some forms of physical interaction by using the Leap Motion and MakeyMakey.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Fun Project" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Fun-Project/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Unity" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Unity/"/>
    
      <category term="Makeymakey" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/Makeymakey/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Spoon Pets</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/08/Spoon-Pets/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/08/Spoon-Pets/</id>
    <published>2019-04-08T06:41:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:40:44.403Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2018 - November 2018]<br>Course: Human-Computer Interaction </p><p>“Spoon Pets” is a conceptual interaction design of an application prototype that helps users develop productivity and overcome procrastination, therefore enables them to foster ethical behaviour. The prototype was built by using Adobe suit and sketch.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>Spoon Pets is a conceptual interaction design of an application that helps users develop productivity and overcome procrastination, therefore enables them to foster ethical behaviour. The system is targeted at procrastinators, including people with poor time-management, low self-discipline and poor memory. The system uses a working method called Pomodoro Technique to assist users to complete their tasks, using a timer to break down work into intervals, traditionally 25 minutes in length, separated by short breaks, while setting limitation in application to control users’ mobile phone and also to remind users what they should do every day. Also, users will be rewarded by virtual coins that allow users to keep virtual pets, which can be later turned into real money to help animals in the streets under the support of Stray Animal Care Organizations. This can act as a motivation to keep users participating. </p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Report PDF- Conceptual Design &amp; Analysis</a><br><a href>Report PDF- Conceptual Design &amp; Prototype</a><br><a href>Report PDF- Evaluation Report</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href>Mobile Interface Design-Spoon Pets</a><br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/2MRf7hP.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Personal Academic Poster</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="Teammates"><a href="#Teammates" class="headerlink" title="Teammates"></a>Teammates</h2><p>Zhijun Tang,Shiqi Zheng, Siying Hu</p><h2 id="My-Contribution"><a href="#My-Contribution" class="headerlink" title="My Contribution"></a>My Contribution</h2><ul><li>Adapt and apply principles of user-interface design;</li><li>Adapt relate cognitive, social, and emotional theories to the design of human-system interaction;</li><li>Apply iterative design techniques such as scenario development, prototyping, and participatory design with teammates</li><li>Learn the role of Qualitative analysis and quantitative analysis.</li><li>Learn the role of evaluation (user and expert) in the development of interactive systems, implement an evaluation framework that is appropriate for a given set of objectives, analyse the results of those evaluation methods in terms of establishing design and system requirements, and report those results and analysis.</li></ul><h2 id="Project-Description"><a href="#Project-Description" class="headerlink" title="Project Description"></a>Project Description</h2><h4 id="Milestone-1-Conceptual-Design-amp-Analysis"><a href="#Milestone-1-Conceptual-Design-amp-Analysis" class="headerlink" title="Milestone 1: Conceptual Design &amp; Analysis"></a>Milestone 1: Conceptual Design &amp; Analysis</h4><p>To comprehend the system and the demand of users, we did a survey online and the face-to-face interview<br>with different types of people. After we researched and analysed those data, we founnd out the main function<br>that user needed and the problem that the existing system and application lacked. In the last, we<br>complete a simple prototype and give the detail and description of our conceptual model. Our process included five steps and we integrated them into the next four sections which are the contextual inquiry, contextual analysis, conceptual model and low fidelity prototype.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/M6tA2gx.png" alt></p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/OZ2ibcn.png" alt></p><h4 id="Milestone-2-Conceptual-Design-amp-Prototype"><a href="#Milestone-2-Conceptual-Design-amp-Prototype" class="headerlink" title="Milestone 2: Conceptual Design &amp; Prototype"></a>Milestone 2: Conceptual Design &amp; Prototype</h4><p>Our team provided a conceptual design for the system that is being developed including a rationale for that design based in the information obtained from the contextual inquiry. It was also incorporate considerations arising from the interaction paradigm, interaction mode, context of use and the results from completing an evaluation of a low fidelity prototype by targeted users, and analysis of the results from that evaluation. In this step, the design process concluded with revised key user needs and goals, and system requirements including our team’s rationale.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/SjhmyaB.png" alt></p><h4 id="Milestone-3-Evaluation"><a href="#Milestone-3-Evaluation" class="headerlink" title="Milestone 3: Evaluation"></a>Milestone 3: Evaluation</h4><p>Our team provided the results of completing evaluations of the interactive system. The evaluations include: usability evaluations such as heuristic evaluations, cognitive walkthroughs and pluralistic evaluations, as well as UX evaluations. The research process incorporate an analysis of the data we had collected (both quantitative and qualitative), outline our primary findings, and provide recommendations. Additionally, the analysis included measures such as success rates, task time and error rates as well as assessment of UX goals.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/NeMuj0W.jpg" alt></p><h2 id="Academic-Poster-Personal-Work"><a href="#Academic-Poster-Personal-Work" class="headerlink" title="Academic Poster [Personal Work]"></a>Academic Poster [Personal Work]</h2><p>This is an academic poster that presents a guide to an HCI concept that I have used during the linked project. The guide draw on my own experience of applying that concept or using that method in research project.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/2MRf7hP.jpg" alt></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2018 - November 2018]&lt;br&gt;Course: Human-Computer Interaction &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Spoon Pets” is a conceptual interaction design of an application prototype that helps users develop productivity and overcome procrastination, therefore enables them to foster ethical behaviour. The prototype was built by using Adobe suit and sketch.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Completed Projects" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Completed-Projects/"/>
    
    
      <category term="App" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/App/"/>
    
      <category term="HCI" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/HCI/"/>
    
      <category term="human-centre design" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/human-centre-design/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Old Queensland</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/07/The-Old-Queensland/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/07/The-Old-Queensland/</id>
    <published>2019-04-07T01:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:41:13.496Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[July 2017 - November 2017]<br>Course: Design Computing Studio 1</p><p>The Old Queensland is an interactive web application built using the State Library of Queensland. SLQ data (<a href="http://data.gov.au/organization/slq)" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://data.gov.au/organization/slq)</a>. The primary audience of this website should be teenagers, especially for the young generation, Our team wish they can use new technology to engage with history. It utilises SLQ data via data.gov.au’s APIs for dynamic searching. The data is divided into three sections on the website, including Image Gallery, News Photo, and Soldier Portrait, users can search and filter preferred information by choosing different years and topic options. The objective of the website is allowing users to explore historical information through various interesting interactions, visualizing digital records and offering an aesthetic visual representation for users. At the meantime, this project tends to provide a better browsing and learning experience for the target customers of the website. </p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>Our team has established an interactive website which is basically a showcase of Queensland’s information during the First World War. The primary audience of this website should be teenagers, the data which applied are all from government databases in Queensland. The data will be divided into three sections on the website, including Image Gallery, News Photo, and Soldier Portrait, users can search and filter preferred information by choosing different years and other options. The objective of the website is allowing users to explore historical information through various interesting interactions, visualizing digital records and offering an aesthetic visual representation for users. At the meantime, this project tends to provide a better browsing and learning experience for the target customers of the website.</p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Code</a><br><a href>Report PDF</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href="https://i.imgur.com/v2Fv9Rg.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Poster</a></p></li></ul><p>####Teammates<br>Changwen Huang, Yihe Zhong, Shunan Ding, Siying Hu</p><h2 id="Project-Description"><a href="#Project-Description" class="headerlink" title="Project Description"></a>Project Description</h2><h4 id="Interesting-Aspect"><a href="#Interesting-Aspect" class="headerlink" title="Interesting Aspect"></a>Interesting Aspect</h4><p>In terms of general impression, history has always been solemn and inviolable. Using the project of our group, the user can be able to cross the time and geographical restriction, browse and access interactive forms of specific historical information. We hope this interactive website can help target audience quering and browsing their interested information more conveniently and effectively. Through the images, photos and other visual design elements to attract potential users to browse our website, search and find information about the history of Queensland in World War I. In the process of browsing, the users will remember and memorize the specific time of important events and warriors.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/iFJw1Ru.png" alt></p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/d1CW7f2.png" alt></p><p>This historical digital interactive website shows the “interactive” animation and historical information which includes integrated science, knowledge and interests. Through digital exhibition interactive, cutting-edge digital content viewing mode and other advanced exhibition methods, the website enables users to experience an impressive journey of technological history. The website becomes more comprehensive and attractive because of the high integration of various elements. Through the combination of video, sound, animation and variety of media methods, it intensively shows the background and significance of Queensland in World War I. The project is expected to bring back historical events, historical figures, historical objects and other historical elements by using the latest design concept and display technology. Through the interaction with this website, history is no longer far away from us or out of people’s imagination, it is being exhibited right in front of the users, granting them a deeper understanding of these classic and unforgettable memories.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Jh0lLrh.png" alt></p><h4 id="Conclusion"><a href="#Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="Conclusion"></a>Conclusion</h4><p>Ultimately, we anticipate this project will promote and encourage users to improve their autonomous learning and digital reading ability by fully using digital reading interactivity. By using the website of digitized historical information, we can cultivate the target groups include teenagers and children to control and apply the advanced learning strategies such as summarization and self-regulation. Finally, these users can make conscious control of their reading motivation and reading strategies, which will help them reading more actively and efficiently through browsing the historical information of digital media.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[July 2017 - November 2017]&lt;br&gt;Course: Design Computing Studio 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Old Queensland is an interactive web application built using the State Library of Queensland. SLQ data (&lt;a href=&quot;http://data.gov.au/organization/slq)&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;http://data.gov.au/organization/slq)&lt;/a&gt;. The primary audience of this website should be teenagers, especially for the young generation, Our team wish they can use new technology to engage with history. It utilises SLQ data via data.gov.au’s APIs for dynamic searching. The data is divided into three sections on the website, including Image Gallery, News Photo, and Soldier Portrait, users can search and filter preferred information by choosing different years and topic options. The objective of the website is allowing users to explore historical information through various interesting interactions, visualizing digital records and offering an aesthetic visual representation for users. At the meantime, this project tends to provide a better browsing and learning experience for the target customers of the website. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Completed Projects" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Completed-Projects/"/>
    
    
      <category term="HCI" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/HCI/"/>
    
      <category term="website" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/website/"/>
    
      <category term="SQL" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/SQL/"/>
    
      <category term="API" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/API/"/>
    
      <category term="JQuery" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/JQuery/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Little Prince</title>
    <link href="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/06/The-Little-Prince/"/>
    <id>https://huhuwithcode.github.io/2019/04/06/The-Little-Prince/</id>
    <published>2019-04-06T01:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-13T15:41:01.480Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[February 2018 - June 2018]<br>Course: Introduction to Web Design</p><p>The Little Prince is an interactive story website for children aged 13 and under. The project aims to design a digital version of a printed “choose users own adventure” book. The entire website was designed through three iterations process to explore how it can most effectively translate the book from physical to digital form.</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction"></a>Introduction</h2><p>The website is basing on a household French story- Little Prince. A poetic tale with watercolour illustrations, this story contains several fantastic adventure experience of the little prince. The little prince, the pilot and the narrator are brought to a desert due to a crashed aircraft, which makes a beginning of the story.</p><ul><li><p>User Study &amp; More Details:<br><a href>Github Code</a><br><a href>Report PDF</a></p></li><li><p>Promotional Material：<br><a href>Graphic Design</a></p></li></ul><h2 id="Project-Description"><a href="#Project-Description" class="headerlink" title="Project Description"></a>Project Description</h2><h4 id="Interesting-Aspect"><a href="#Interesting-Aspect" class="headerlink" title="Interesting Aspect"></a>Interesting Aspect</h4><p>This story is basically a reflection on Saint-Exupéry’s own experience in the Sahara in a fairy tale writing style. What makes the story well-known and extraordinary is the critical social aspect. This story reflects human nature instead of a simple fiction adventure, describing an absurd adult world. People in various ages are inclined to make different understanding and reflection on this story. The six people that the prince meets are meant to critique an appearance of society. The king without subjects desire for followers, which is quite similarly with some politicians who are not capable of management talent but to pursue power in their life. Besides, a businessman who ignores the beauty of stars and keeps counting them with a perverted value in this story is same as some people who desire for wealth and material possessions without interest in spiritual matters. These people are all typical symbols in reality.</p><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/f3XzJ58.png" alt></p><h4 id="The-Audience"><a href="#The-Audience" class="headerlink" title="The Audience"></a>The Audience</h4><p>Commonly, people consider The Little Prince as a children’s book. In the matter of fact, many adults continue to cling to this story long after childhood, which means that the audience is of all ages( ，2005). Young children would find it an interesting and imaginative story while adults tend to understand this story in different perspectives, combining their life experiences. Everyone could find something in common with the six strange people. The process of grown-ups equals to the time of understanding this story. This story is especially suitable for every child and some adults who lost their innocence and thinking ability. The prince cares for colours of a small house, a common but beautiful flower and the relationship between others, which often ignored by grown-ups. People are supposed to care about each other, cherish what’s really important for them, and be grateful for the happiness that they’ve gained. We all believe knowledge and experience enable us to see clearly and make right judgements all the time. But we may sometimes lose the right to speak straight forwardly, think creatively or love courageously resulting from what we’ve experienced. We all once have those doubts the little prince has, and the story reminds us of these doubts when we grow up. This website is intention to display this story again for touching the soul and arousing thinking. Only to hope that people can be aware of the simplicity of life. ( Wikipedia,2017)</p><h4 id="Conclusion"><a href="#Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="Conclusion"></a>Conclusion</h4><p>With the development of society, people are inclined to be a ‘grown-up’, ignoring the beauty and simplicity. We are supposed to care about each other, cherish what’s really important for them. This website based on the story the Little Prince intends to display this story again for touching the soul and arousing thinking. Only to hope that people can be aware of the simplicity of life.  </p><h2 id="Project-Process"><a href="#Project-Process" class="headerlink" title="Project Process"></a>Project Process</h2><h4 id="User-Persona"><a href="#User-Persona" class="headerlink" title="User Persona"></a>User Persona</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/mf1APCP.png" alt></p><h4 id="Site-Map"><a href="#Site-Map" class="headerlink" title="Site Map"></a>Site Map</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/0WvCGUS.png" alt></p><h4 id="Wireframe"><a href="#Wireframe" class="headerlink" title="Wireframe"></a>Wireframe</h4><ul><li><p>Home Page<br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/ZXmTjd5.png" alt></p></li><li><p>Media Page<br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/LH0fokU.png" alt></p></li></ul><h4 id="Card-Sorting"><a href="#Card-Sorting" class="headerlink" title="Card Sorting"></a>Card Sorting</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Gku27lE.jpg" alt></p><h4 id="Paper-Prototype-Testing"><a href="#Paper-Prototype-Testing" class="headerlink" title="Paper Prototype Testing"></a>Paper Prototype Testing</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/RSO7dxn.jpg" alt></p><h4 id="Website-High-Fidelity-User-Testing"><a href="#Website-High-Fidelity-User-Testing" class="headerlink" title="Website High Fidelity User Testing"></a>Website High Fidelity User Testing</h4><p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/9OhBzX2.png" alt></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;[February 2018 - June 2018]&lt;br&gt;Course: Introduction to Web Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Little Prince is an interactive story website for children aged 13 and under. The project aims to design a digital version of a printed “choose users own adventure” book. The entire website was designed through three iterations process to explore how it can most effectively translate the book from physical to digital form.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Fun Project" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/categories/Fun-Project/"/>
    
    
      <category term="HCI" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/HCI/"/>
    
      <category term="website" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/website/"/>
    
      <category term="children" scheme="https://huhuwithcode.github.io/tags/children/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
